Saaya!
Oh, Saneatsu.
I met with Sudo Senpai.
What?!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
You want to change our plans?
Yes.
Saneatsu didn't have enough time
to search for postboxes, so...
He wants to search this
area again in the afternoon.
Sup!
Sato-kun!
I'm like Saneatsu!
You can call me Kazuhiko!
Come on, give it a go.
Wah!
So childish.
Not quite!
Senpai.
Senpai, you opened my
envelope of Rights, didn't you?
Wha—
I'm not mad or anything.
I just wanted to ask for the truth.
Y-Yeah, so what? It made no sense!
It said something about "compliance",
whatever that means.
So there's no risk involving normal Rights...
S-Sorry.
Never mind that, Senpai.
Could you try telling me
to "raise my right arm"?
Raise your right arm.
Senpai, now try the left side.
Why? What's this for?
Don't do it. Don't do it.
Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it!
Raise your left arm.
I stopped it! Just like I thought.
Prime Rights have absolute force
while Rights don't.
With enough willpower,
Rights can be negated!
Hey! What was all that about?
Um, so it looks like you've gained
the Right of Compliance.
Think of it like magic powers
to make others obey your command.
That's... awesome!
I don't like that look!
Thanks for teaching me this stuff.
You know, Sensei said you weren't too smart,
but I think you catch on quick.
Sure...
All right, let's start our afternoon search!
We'll meet back up at 5:00pm!
According to the map,
it should be around here...
Like I thought!
Fujishiro-san, ya said
something about a favor...
You see...
Sorry I'm late!
Jeez, Sorry-atsu!
Narita, have you seen Fujishiro?
No... Is something the matter?
She hasn't come back yet.
It's already past five.
Let's wait. If we leave here now,
she may never be able to find us.
You're right...
I second that.
Mm-yup.
So what? Should we search this area again?
Or... Maybe we should think of what to do
if Saaya doesn't come back, don't you think?
Fujishiro-san's favor... This is it!
Yeah, he's right. We gotta decide
at what point to move on.
Perfect, he got my sign.
He's following my lead.
That's true...
We can't wait forever, and we need
to make the call sooner or later.
Then we could wait till midnight...
Or! A bit later?
Then let's wait here until 5:00am.
How's that sound?
Mm-yup.
Good. So the time limit
is 5:00am tomorrow morning.
What?! You've found the postbox for today?
That's right. The questions
have been submitted, too.
Wh-What sort of questions?
I included a few questions
to test the waters.
"Wooden structures or non-wooden structures?"
The third ensures
that we're in the minority.
"Dyed rainbow hair or light-green hair?"
"Age 40 under or over?"
So there's no need to search
for postboxes today.
Focus on identifying the infiltrator.
It's about time. There's a question coming.
It's time. We will now begin
tallying the majority.
I reject.
Prime Rights: 12 left
Rights: 45 left
40 years of age
Under or Over
1,081,990 people left
Sudo Senpai was right!
This means questions can only target people,
and questions that leave room
for other responses become null.
Nakano Ward
Today's Area
We've passed midnight.
Itabashi Ward
We made it!
Hey, guys. What do you say we choose
our routes for tomorrow ahead of time?
We'll be waiting for Saaya
until the last minute.
Might as well come up with a plan
to make things smoother tomorrow.
Mm-yup. I'm on board.
Sensei, could you take the lead?
S-Sure...
We'll search north of Narimasu Station
along the Tobu Tojo Line in the morning.
Then go to Ukimafunado Station along
the Saikyo Line in the afternoon.
And pass through Tokiwadai to head to
City Hall in the evening to spend the night.
That way, we can do
a widespread search efficiently
and end the day in the inner city.
Great. Let's go with that route tomorrow.
Let me practice in my mind...
Great, I'll be right back.
Huh?
I'm just going to the bathroom!
Okay, "Dump-atsu".
N.S. here, calling F.S. on standby.
Route incoming. Follow along with map...
I'll contact you through the radio
station that's still functional.
Set the frequency to this and wait
for my call with the radio turned on.
Why didn't you come back, Saaya?
Just when I thought we were getting close!
I doubt she can search
for postboxes in that state...
Kunashiri, you stay here and—
Oh my God! Leave me alone!
So here's how we'll split up.
I'll search north.
Jin, you look on the west side.
Narita, you head south.
Sato, you go east.
Don't see one anywhere...
I finally found you, traitor!
Huh? S-Sensei?
What? Traitor?
Souma!
Don't cause a scene.
I've been looking for you...
Owner of the Rejection Right.
Earlier this year, a source told me I could
find the owner of the Rejection Right
at Suginami Daini High School...
I did everything in my power
to gather information from them
and transfer to the school.
Sudo's outburst was based on his assumption
that you were the Emperor.
Only one thing could warrant that...
You're the owner of a Prime Right!
The Rejection Right to be exact!
Everyday, while your team
was helpless before Tasuketsu...
You were exercising your Rejection Right
to exempt yourself, weren't you?
If that's not betraying your friends, what is?
This man is Souma, owner of a Prime Right
with the Production Attribute.
Do as he says, and you
and your friends will be safe.
If you refuse, we have no choice
but to use Souma's Prime Right.
You know what to do
if you care about your friends.
Right, traitor?
No, you're the traitor, Shinozaki Sensei!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Narita? You were listening?
Yes, from the very beginning.
Yesterday, Sudo Senpai told me
about an infiltrator in our group...
which brings us here.
What do you mean?
Senpai also suspected Omi was the Emperor.
Omi... you've been wearing those
earphones since we met back up.
And you've had that band-aid on
your right cheek since we first met.
Senpai's theory is this:
Omi Jin exchanged the hearing
in his right ear for a Prime Right.
And you, Sensei...
Could you take your glasses off?
You sacrificed your right eye
in exchange for a Prime Right
related to vision, didn't you?
That day we first came
together as a group...
How did the President arrive
at school earlier than everyone else
when the trains were stopped?
You must have driven him there.
That's ridiculous.
Why on earth would I pick up Yagihashi
when I don't even know
if he saw the original question?
For starters, I saw the same
screen you two saw.
See, that's just an assumption.
The test run never said the screens
were displayed simultaneously worldwide.
I heard from Saaya.
Apparently, you told the President
to digitize the contact network.
And you authorized using the computer
science classroom outside school hours
and even supervised it.
In that case, it's entirely possible
that the first question
happened to pop up during your time there.
Even after the President's death,
you remained the assistant leader,
as if there was no other choice.
And next you were planning
what to do about Saaya,
so I asked her to leave the group yesterday.
So I could observe what you'd do in response.
Isn't that a bit much, Narita? Sacrificing
Fujishiro just to expose my plans?
She's actually not missing at all.
Impossible!
I've already contacted her
through radio transmission.
We decided our route yesterday, remember?
Radio transmission?
What's going on here?!
Sensei, I heard you told Eren Senpai
that I'm not smart, but you should know...
I'm actually known for my brains
and athletic skill in my class.
Although I'm Sorry-atsu
when it comes to computers.
Of all people...
I was ambushed by Narita?!
If there's anything else you're hiding,
please tell us now.
And I hope you change
from the bottom of your heart.
Traitor or not, you're still our teacher.
Unfortunately, that's not an option...
Prime Right of Visualization...
With this, I can search for postboxes.
Anyone that gets in the way will be
eliminated with Souma's Prime Right.
And with Jin's Prime Right,
we can be exempt from Tasuketsu.
He's wrong. The Rejection
Right can't be used by others.
After that, all I need is higher ground
to watch over the city.
Listen to me!
He's been exempting himself
from Tasuketsu all along!
Which makes him just as much of a trait—
What a bunch of crap!
There's no doubt in my mind
that Omi helped us!
He's nothing like you
who only looks after himself!
You coward!
I'll kill you.
Souma! Get hi—
Kazuhiko! Take Omi and run!
Prime Right of Materialization!
No way!
All right, Yoshida-san No. 1: finish him.
To hell with that!
Run! Hurry!
Faster, faster, faster!
Omi... did he get away in time?
Was I able to save him?
I don't wanna die yet!
Without defeating the Emperor... I can't die!
Someone! Help me!
Well, if you ever need anything
just lemme know.
We're best friends, after all.
Good thing I wasn't late today!
"Good thing" my ass! Tardy Monster!
What is that?
What the heck is this thing?!
S-Saaya?!
Run, Eren Senpai! I'll hold them off!
No way!
President?
I'll explain later!
Get in the shadows!
B-But...
Don't be stupid! Let's go, Saaya!
Sweet dreams. For eternity.
Die.
You two! Cover your heads and get down!
This is the end.
What's that?
A fireproof cloak.
I like to keep one on me.
Thanks for your help, Sudo-kun.
No need to thank me.
As you may have already noticed,
I've heard everything from Sudo-kun.
But how did you know where we were?
The radio.
Anyways, what is this thing?
I'm assuming Saneatsu couldn't
get a confession out of Sensei
and this was the result.
Sensei? Confess? What about?
Don't worry, Fujishiro-san.
We sent Narita-kun's best friend
Ichinose-kun his way.
He also possesses a Prime Right.
Saneatsu's best friend...
No need to stay here any longer.
Hey, what about Sensei?
Confess to what? Am I the
only one out of the loop?
I'll explain on the way there, Senpai.
Were we too late?!
Yagi-chan and Sudocchi
were supposed to be here,
so they must've taken
the girls and evacuated.
Yagi-chan...
Crud, someone saw me...
A survivor!
Um, h-hello...
You're the first person I've met besides
my teammates, so I'm not sure what to say...
'Scuse us! We're looking
for someone. Do you mind?
Hey, don't!
Who cares? We might as well.
Um, so... Have you seen a girl
with pigtails anywhere?
Nah.
Then how about... A short boy
with earphones wearing a hoodie?
Follow me.
Narimasu Market
It's not Omi?
Here ya go. They're that kid's friends.
So, the owner of the Rejection
Right is named Omi?
Just so you know, I have a Prime Right
called the Right of Fusion, so...
Y-You idiot!
Better watch what you say
if you don't wanna be taken out.
I'm Miwa Isshiki,
and this here is Rika Suzuki.
She and I are Prime Right owners, as well.
Sorry, but we won't be introducing
ourselves until we can trust you.
How do you know about Omi
and the Right of Rejection?
After the Tasuketsu on "male or female",
Rika-chan and I met Omi-kun
in front of a blue postbox.
Although I suppose he and I didn't
exactly become acquaintances.
After Omi-kun submitted his question,
Rika-chan fell and got terribly hurt.
So I showed her the Prime Right
envelope I had on hand.
Which I guess ended up saving my life.
But hey, you were the one
who shocked me in the first place!
So that was the sacrifice...
Yeah, that reminds me.
They make you exchange a healthy
body part in return for a Prime Right.
There are instructions
when you open the envelope.
A screen pops up out of nowhere.
Isn't that cool?
Rika-chan's Prime Right
is the Right of Evasion.
She can completely avoid any physical
dangers that may threaten her.
Not too shabby, is it?
Although it excludes Tasuketsu.
If it weren't for me, you'd have
been dead from that explosion.
It wouldn't hurt to show
a bit more appreciation.
You know I do.
Sucks that my leg didn't make it, though.
Omi-kun's question was
about reviving past victims.
So it really was Omi!
And... the second question
to kill them again was mine.
The Prime Right of Re-execution...
The ability to reenact certain
information and Prime Rights,
excluding physical phenomena.
In case Omi-kun's question became nullified,
the first question was for restoration.
The second question was to set re-execution
at 12:05am and enforcement at 12:10am.
You are currently looking at this
screen in Tokyo Prefecture
You bitch!
You mean to tell me Mom and Dad
died because of you?! Screw you!
Just kidding!
Huh?
I've already processed my feelings,
and besides, they'll always be in my heart.
Ha! Like they all say when someone
dies in the middle of the story!
"They'll be in my heart"?
More like "their cells are
literally fused within my body"!
Which, by the way,
just between you and me...
Even if I'm part of the majority in Tasuketsu,
all I need to do to survive is fuse
my cells with the minority group!
But that's a secret!
Who are you talking to?
I don't fully trust you.
But if there's something in it for us,
we'll talk. How's that sound?
I'll tell you everything I know,
but I have a favor to ask in return.
A favor?
Kill Mido.
K-Kill...
Mido and Ren Iruga.
Those two are dangerous,
but especially Mido...
I don't know his location or motive
or even his first name.
But I know he's up to something.
Someone has to stop him.
Kill... someone...
Sure, no prob!
So whatcha got in terms of info?
Hey! Ryuta, come on!
Worst case scenario,
leave it to me. Don't worry.
What?!
We haven't gathered any information so far.
I can take on some risk
if that's what it's worth.
Ryuta...
Tasuketsu and Prime Rights go hand
in hand. That can't be overstated.
Of them, the strongest
Prime Right is Obedience,
Right of Obedience
and next in line is the Rejection Right.
Right of Rejection
Permission
Both are powers relating
to the ability of permission.
I only know a portion of Prime Rights
held by some of the older owners.
Older owners? What does that mean?
That's a question better suited for
your classmate with the Rejection Right.
I don't want to share anything
they'd rather not disclose.
Funny how Prime Rights work...
It's almost like a reflection of their owners.
They never even told us
their names, after all.
That's all right.
Well, I guess I'll go make my rounds.
Maybe I'd be better off in a wheelchair...
Finally, there's some hope...
I thought you might be alive! Hiya!
Don't you move a muscle.
Aw, man. I told you not to move.
Too bad.
Motion